poolexpert.com 2018-05-25

# Fantasy NHL Hockey and MLB Baseball Pool Manager

PoolExpert has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for all PoolExpert' Web sites.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We take the security issue very seriously, and will always do our best to protect our visitors. However, no security mechanism is perfect and all visitors must understand that there are always risks that the personal information you send to PoolExpert may be intercepted by others through no fault of our own. PoolExpert is not responsible for such security breaches so long as it is not due to negligence on our part.

## What information does our web site collect from you?

Under some circumstances (for example if you create a hockey pool on PoolExpert), PoolExpert requires that you submit your name, mailing address, and certain other personal information when filling out our registration form. However, any time that PoolExpert wishes to collect such information, you will be warned in advance. PoolExpert will always allow you to view the information that we have on file about you. You will also be able to make changes (eg. Address changes) to your profile whenever you like. Please e-mail [support@poolexpert.com](mailto:support@poolexpert.com) for any such requests.

## Why does our site need this information?

Collecting this data allows us to quickly and easily contact you. For example, we may need to notify you of technical issues, or if you win a prize using one of our sites (eg. PoolExpert). If you like, we can also keep you informed of new products and services being offered by PoolExpert, but we will always give you the choice of whether you wish to receive this type of information or not.

PoolExpert would like to make it clear that none of our advertisers, clients, or partners have access to your personal data, unless you have specifically consented to it. In addition, PoolExpert will never disclose your personal data to any outside party without your knowledge and consent except under the most exceptional circumstances such as: police authorities force us to by law/warrant; it is required for PoolExpert to protect ourselves against actions taken against us which threaten our rights and/or property, or those of our visitors, clients, partners, advertisers, or retailers.

Our sites provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us by sending email to [support@poolexpert.com](mailto:support@poolexpert.com)

## External Links

PoolExpert' Web sites contain links to other sites. Clicking on any of these links will take you away from our site. PoolExpert is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Any personal information that you submit to these sites are subject only to the privacy policies that they offer. PoolExpert is not responsible for privacy breakdowns which occur on other sites.

## Public Forums

PoolExpert's Web sites may contain forums, message boards, and/or news groups. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. PoolExpert is not responsible for privacy breakdowns which occur on public forums.

## Third Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies to collect data and/or serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information but not personal informational ( your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may also use non-cookie technologies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record information about your web surfing activity including your activities on or off this Web site. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these non-cookie technologies, and those browser settings that block cookies may have no effect on such techniques. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit <http://networkadvertising.org/>

## Children

Currently, all PoolExpert' Web sites are available to any and all visitors, and we do not exclude anyone from using our sites based on their age (which we usually don't know anyway). However, if we notice that a minor has sent us any private information through one of our sites, we would try, if possible, to inform the minor's parents by e-mail that their child had done so.

## Cookies

A cookie is information that a Web site puts on your hard disk so that it can remember something about you at a later time. For example, if you are visiting a site that offers you the choice of French or English text, cookies can be used to remember your choice for the next time that you visit the site. Our advertising agent uses cookies to keep a record of the ad banners that have been â??served' to you so that you will not see the same ads over and over.

The use of cookies has become standard practice in the world of Internet browsing. Browsers often come already setup to accept them. Cookies are harmless. You can view the cookies that have been stored on your hard disk (although the content stored in each cookie may not make much sense to you). The location of the cookies depends on the browser. Internet Explorer stores each cookie as a separate file under a Windows subdirectory. Netscape stores all cookies in a single cookies.txt fle. You always have control over the cookies in your computer. You can delete them, or change your preferences to not allow the use of cookies in your computer at all. This will limit the options available to you on certain sites, and will exclude you fromusing certain sites that require cookies to operate properly.

PoolExpert uses cookies to send information which might be usefull to our marketing service, and to deliver content specific to your interests, for example, it is by using cookies that PoolExpertsaves your poolname, which means that you don't need to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

## Reservation of Rights

PoolExpert reserves the right to modify our privacy policies. We suggest that you check this privacy statement from time to time to verify our position on privacy. That being said, the spirit of this statement will never change; we will always take the privacy issue seriously and will always do whatever is necessary to protect our visitors', clients', and affiliates' privacy.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of PoolExpert' web sites, or your dealings with those Web sites, you can contact us by email at: [support@poolexpert.com](mailto:support@poolexpert.com).
